I was just sitting here eating my chicken and waffles and it dawned on me. Y'all the ones
obsessed with sex. Like when we talk about pride and the LGBTQIA plus community, it seems to always
turn into if we teach our children that people like this exist, then we're sexualizing the
children. And it's like, but why is it about sex? It's not about, oh, these people like to have sex
with these people, et cetera. It's really about these people love these people. So why is it that
when we talk about heteronormative scenarios, that it's about love? Mom and dad love each other.
Husband and wife love each other. Boy and girl love each other. But when we talk about the LGBTQIA plus
community, it's simply about sex. That's y'all. That's y'all who are against and who don't agree
with and who don't believe in a lifestyle. Y'all are the ones obsessed with sex. What we really
need to do is be aware of the fact that the people who are making the way people love into
an issue about sex, they're the ones who are grooming. Cause what's wrong with you that you
look at certain people and only think about sex? I think that's an issue you need to deal
with yourself and take that issue out of the classroom.
Mm-hmm.